AHMED HEZQIAL ZAIDAN

Bekasi, Indonesia 17411 | +62882008583981 | hezqilrahmady@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahmedhezqialzaidan

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a qualified fresh graduate majoring in Informatics with internship experience in the field of informatics. Has the enthusiasm to continue learning and adapting to the latest developments in the information technology industry, active in competitions and activities at the university.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. PUPUK SRIWIDJAJA PALEMBANG

Staff Magang IT Dep. Mitra Bisnis & Layanan TI

September 2022 – Desember 2022

- Conducting a Bootcamp on Data Management in Databases
- Manage and Connect User Data into the Database
- Connecting Provincial API in Indonesia to Website Features
- Successfully Managed DAPENSRI User Database
- Successfully Developed Features in the DAPENSRI Application
- Practice Responsibility and Communication at Work

INSTITUT STIAMI

IT Support

September 2017 – November 2017

- Mikrotik Lan Cable Troubleshooting
- Manage Student Database to Connect to University Wifi Data
- Overcoming hardware problems in staff and student rooms
- Helping the IT Team in Managing the Internet Network

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

UNIVERSITAS AHMAD DAHLAN

Bachelor Of Informatics – IPK 3.64 / 4.00

September 2019 – Desember 2023

- Relevant Courses: Basic Computer Systems, Basic Programming, Web Programming, Databases, Data Communications & Computer Networks, Mobile Programming
- BRIN BARISTA Scholarship Recipient (Research Assistance for Research & Innovation Talents) 2022

SMK YADIKA 6

Computer and Network Engineering

Mei 2016 - Mei 2019

• Relevant Courses: Computer Skills and Information Management, Web Programming

TECHNICAL CAPABILITY

- Programming Language: HTML/CSS, PHP, MySQL,C#
- Framework : Laravel
- Application: Visual Studio Code, Sublime Text, Unity, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Canva, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel.
- Language : Indonesia, Inggris

PERSONAL ABILITY

- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Analysis dan Problem Solving
- Effective Communication Skills
- Creative and Disciplined
- Time Management

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Graphic Design At RCC

January 2024 – April 2024

- Successfully Managed RCC Social Media
- Successfully Created a Simple Company Portfolio Website
- Successfully Documenting and Editing Company Activities

2D Game Application Development

August 2023 – October 2023

- Successfully Developed an Arabic Educational Game for Learning Hijaiyah Letters for Grades 1 and 2 at SD Muhammadiyah Karangkajen 4 Yogyakarta
- Developing applications using the Unity application with the C programming language
- Developing Game Assets Using Adobe Illustrator

Graphic Design KKN

February 2023 – March 2023

- Successfully Managed KKN Instagram, Created Organizational Structure Chart for KKN Group
- Successfully documented activities during KKN, edited KKN activities and uploaded them to KKN social media
- Successfully created a simple website to manage village population data
- Successfully created a village video profile to document the profile and activities in the village

UMKM Video Profile Competition

February 2023

- Successfully became 1st place in Bantul Regency
- Responsible as Head of Project, Cameraman, Editor, and Idea in the Flow of the Video to be Made

Barbershop Website Development

May 2022 – July 2022

- Responsible for being the Head of a Website Development Project at a Barbershop in Sleman,

Yogyakarta

- Discuss related features that will be developed on the website with clients
- Monitor the progress of the website being created and ensure that the website created meets client requests

Dahlan Muda Creative Video Competition

September 2019

- Successfully Became 2nd Place at the University in the Creative Video Contest